[{"answer": "Well ah, my friend was, well not a nice person", "docId": "320towdh.htm.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You get the dollhouse", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Oh, she was a cruel, cranky, old bitch!   And I'm sorry she died.  Did Dad say I get the dollhouse", "docId": "320towdh.htm.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I get the dollhouse", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Wow, a house for dolls, that is so cool!  When I was kid, I had a barrel", "docId": "320towdh.htm.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No, just a barrel", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Oh, nothing, he's just goofy like that, I actually, hardly notice it anymore", "docId": "320towdh.htm.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No!!  No!  He's not married, or involved, with anyone", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " And I ate the food, I had the fish, it was good, yeah. It was good, yeah..", "docId": "320towdh.htm.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh, hey!  my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "He happens to be brilliant.  Which is more than I can say for that sweater you're dating", "docId": "320towdh.htm.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I don't care.  Why, do you want me to care", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Hey, I'm not interested in her sweater!  It's what's underneath her sweater that counts.  And besides, since ah, since when do you care who I'm going out with", "docId": "320towdh.htm.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Do you want me to want you to care", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I don't care.  Why, do you want me to care", "docId": "320towdh.htm.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Do you", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah, with the mug painting.  Yeah.  I was so listening to that.  But ah, y'know what, I think I kinda need to work on my stuff tonight", "docId": "320towdh.htm.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Okay.", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend, would you please climb out of my butt.  Why hasn't he called, my friend?  Why", "docId": "320towdh.htm.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Awkward?  Why should he feel awkward", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "So I ah, talked to my friend, kinda told her how things were with us.  Did you ah, did you talk to my friend", "docId": "320towdh.htm.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Y'know, about what happened with us", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "It was, wasn't it", "docId": "320towdh.htm.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Wasn't it", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Look, I'm sorry.  Okay?  I'm weak, and pathetic, and sorry", "docId": "320towdh.htm.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Ahhh", "qsentId": 26}]